Linn Pagès Billai

Enginering student in Media Technology



linnpagesbillai@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/linn-pagès-billai/

Currently, I am completing my master at KTH and planning to graduate at the end of October 2021. I recently finished my master thesis project were the goal was to design a more usable privacy policy by developing a prototype in Figma and evaluate it by conducting user tests. I have a special interest in UX Design and user research.

EDUCATION

Engineer in Media Technology

KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Aug 2015 - Nov 2021

Degree programme in Media Technology with a master in Interactive Media Technology with specialisation track Visual Media.

CAREER

UX Designer

THS Consultant

Sep 2019 - Jan 2020

Designed a clickable prototype in Figma as part of a team with the purpose of developing a mobile application. Held meetings with client to ensure that the clients requirements were fulfilled.

Store Manager

Tvättstället

Jun 2013 - Dec 2017

Store manager with focus on customer and cash management.

EXPERIENCE

Head of Technlogy & Logistics

Media Career Day

Apr 2017 - Nov 2017

In charge of logistics and technology during the career fair.

SKILLS

Figma, Marvel, User research, CSS, HTML, Javascript, React.js, XML, Python, SQL